# Enzo Fassioli

Alpharetta, GA 30004 (305) 282-9897 zoefassioli@gmail.com LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/enzo-fassioli/ GitHub:

https://github.com/enzofass

Portfolio:

https://enzofass.github.io/Portfolio-July-2019/

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Electrical Controls Engineer** — Futura North America Inc.

Alpharetta, GA

APRIL 2015 - APRIL 2019 && FEB 2011 - NOV 2013

Handled majority of customer electrical and controls issues in North America. Allen Bradley and Siemens PLC programming and debugging of complex industrial automation controls systems. HMI programming and debugging, AC / DC drives.

## **Associate Controls Engineer** — Mesh Automation

Cumming, GA

NOV 2013 - APRIL 2015

PLC / HMI programming, Electrical control system design and spec, system validation, process control for Class 1 Div 2 area.

#### **PROJECTS**

# [/bakət/] — Bucket List Creator / Organizer

Full-Stack app that allows you to create an account and add bucket list items to your profile. You can mark items complete and keep track of your progress. HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Node.js | Express.js | MySQL | Sequelize | JWT | Bcrypt

## **SoundCheck** — *Spotify Playlist Generator*

This front-end dependent app allows the user to search an artist/band the query will generate a list of upcoming performances. User can select an upcoming show and it will generate and save a Spotify playlist to user's account.

HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | JavaScript | Spotify API | Bands In Town API | Bearer Token

# LIRI Bot — Command Line Assistant

This command line assistant takes in a set of keywords and renders results from serval API's to the command prompt.

Node.js | Express.js | Bands In Town API | Spotify API | OMDB API

## **EDUCATION**

# Georgia Institute of Technology — Atlanta, Ga

Full-Stack Web Development

APRII 2019 - JULY 2019

#### **ITT Technical Institute** — Duluth, Ga

Computer Electronics Engineering Technology

JUNE 2008 - JUNE 2010

#### **SUMMARY**

Former Electrical Controls Engineer with 8+ years of experience and proven knowledge of working in a team, industrial troubleshooting, and problem-solving, turned M.E.R.N. Full Stack Web Developer. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the Web Developer role at your company.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Fluent in: English / Spanish / Italian

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML / CSS (Bootstrap, Grid)

JavaScript (JQuery)

React.js

Node.js / Express.js

MySQL / Sequelize

MongoDB / Mongoose

Git / GitHub / Git Bash

8+ years complex troubleshooting

8+ years technical problem solving

8+ years technical customer support

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Collaborative and able to work in teams or groups

Motivated and always willing to learn new skills

Independent and self-sufficient in handling tasks

Good verbal and written communication skills